Finding aid for the Nathan Pritikin papers LSC.1628
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Books By or About Nathan Pritikin
  - Books: Unpublished, Miscellaneous
    - Donald Monkerud (Box 11)
      (See also Box no.21: Athletes: Runner's World columns)
- Diseases
  - Alternative Therapies
    - New concepts of normality for blood values and nutritional composition. (Box 12)
    - Dietary supplements. (Box 12)
    - Chelation therapy. (Box 12)
    - Hydrogen peroxide perfusion. (Box 12)
    - "Magic drugs." (Box 12)
  - Miscellaneous Pathologies
    - Response to Pritikin Program (diverse conditions). (Box 12)
    - ALS. (Box 12)
    - Ankylosing Spondylitis. (Box 12)
    - Crohn's Disease. (Box 12)
    - Alzheimer's. (Box 12)
    - Lupus. (Box 12)
    - Migraine headaches. (Box 12)
    - Mitral valve disorder. (Box 12)
    - Multiple sclerosis. (Box 12)
    - Polycythemia rubra vera. (Box 12)
    - Parkinson's disease. (Box 12)
    - Psoriatic arthritis. (Box 12)
    - Spasm. (Box 12)
  - Allergies
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
  - Artery closure
    - Reversal. (Box 12)
  - Arthritis
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
  - Cancer
    - Breast cancer. (Box 12)
    - Colon cancer. (Box 12)
  - Dental Problems
    - Dental caries; gingivitis; gum disease. (Box 12)
  - Diabetes: Pritikin's Work With Diabetics
    - Pritikin's advice to diabetics. (Box 12)
    - Juvenile diabetes patients. (Box 12)
    - Experimentation with fructose drinks with diabetics. (Box 12)
    - Comments by others re effectiveness of Pritikin diet for diabetics. (Box 12)
  - Diabetes: Contact With Diabetes Researchers: Dr. James Anderson
    - 1980-1983. (Box 12)
    - 1978-1979. (Box 12)
    - 1976-1977. (Box 12)
    - Anderson approached by Pritikin; funding obtained; Study completed. (Box 12)
    - Anderson papers, abstracts and talks. (Box 12)
  - Diabetes: Contact With Other Diabetes Researchers and ADA
    - Joslyn Diabetic Foundation. (Box 12)
    - Rachmiel Levine, M.D. (Box 12)
    - Shirley Masaoka, M.D. (Box 12)
    - Mayer Davidson, M.D. (Box 12)
    - McMillan, Donald E., M.D. (Box 12)
    - David Robbins, M.D. (Box 12)
    - Israel Rabinowitch, M.D. (Box 12)
    - American Diabetes Association. (Box 12)
  - Diabetes: Soliciting Support for Concept That Diet is Cause of Type II Diabetes, etc.
    - Berk correspondence. (Box 12)
    - Kroc Foundation. (Box 12)
    - Request for funds for diabetic study. (Box 12)
    - People receiving diabetes manuscript. (Box 12)
    - Institutions contacted to conduct diabetic study. (Box 12)
      (See also: Box no.8, contact with diabetes researchers)
  - Diabetes: Kirsten Foundation: Dr. Melvin Wiedman
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
      (See also: Long Beach Study results)
    - K---- and L---- G----; Kirsten Foundation Correspondence. (Box 12)
    - Kirsten Foundation: Financial support for LFC & Long Beach Studies. (Box 12)
  - Diabetes: Support for Dr. Paul Lacy's Work With Islet Transplants (Washington University, St. Louis, Missouri)
    - Islet Transplant Study - Paul Lacy, M.D. Correspondence, research reports and notes. (Box 12)
    - Research at Barbara Davis Center for Childhood Diabetes with fetal tissue transplants. (Box 12)
    - Barbara and Marvin Davis: Funds sought for diabetic research. (Box 12)
  - Diabetes: Pritikin's Letters to Members of U.S. Congress (February 22, 1982) and to Health Editors
    - Nathan Pritikin Letter (); Replies by Congressmen., February 22, 1982 (Box 12)
    - Nathan Pritikin Letter to health editors. (Box 12)
  - Diabetes: Writings by Nathan or Staff
    (See also: Box no.6A, vol.3, Diabetes)
    - Miles Robinson, M.D. - Monogram on diabetes for PRF. (Box 12)
    - Miles Robinson, M.D. - Book Promotion: Pritikin statement on diabetes. (Box 12)
    - Miscellaneous writings and studies by Pritikin associates. (Box 12)
    - Attempts to publish diabetes manuscript and early results with diabetics. (Box 12)
  - Foot Problems
    - "Walk, Don't Run" - Wikler. (Box 12)
  - Gastrointestinal Disorders
    - Celiac disease. (Box 12)
    - Colitis. (Box 12)
    - Constipation: N.P. Protocol. (Box 12)
  - Hearing Loss
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
  - Heart Disease
    - Heart disease reversal claim by N.P. (Box 12)
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
  - Hypertension
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
    - Hypertension monograph by Dr. Miles Robinson for PRF. (Box 12)
  - Kidney Disease
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
  - Longevity
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
  - Obesity
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
  - Osteoporosis
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
  - Senility
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
  - Sickle-Cell Disease
    - Personal writings. (Box 12)
  - Skin Disorders
    - Psoriasis. (Box 12)
  - Stroke
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
  - Tumors
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
  - Visual Problems
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
- Government
  - State of California: Governor's Council on Wellness & Physical Fitness
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
  - State of California: Department of Health
    - [No further description available]. (Box 12)
    - Seminar. (Box 13)
  - State of Louisiana
    (See also: Box no.32, Pritikin Research Foundation studies, "Natchitoches")
    - [No further description available]. (Box 13)
  - U.S. Dietary Guidelines
    - School lunch program. (Box 13)
    - Dietary Guidelines Advisory Committee. (Box 13)
    - U.S. Guidelines (Revised) -, September 1985. (Box 13)
    - Medicaid (nursing and convalescent homes). (Box 13)
  - U.S. Congress: Individual Members
    - Frank Annunzio. (Box 13)
    - Senator Henry Bellmon. (Box 13)
    - President Jimmy Carter. (Box 13)
    - Senator Alan Cranston. (Box 13)
    - Senator Jake Garn. (Box 13)
    - Senator Orrin Hatch. (Box 13)
    - Senator Richard Lugar. (Box 13)
    - Senator Robert Mollohan. (Box 13)
    - Senator George McGovern. (Box 13)
    - Senator William Proxmire. (Box 13)
    - Senator Richard Schweiker. (Box 13)
    - Congressman Henry Waxman. (Box 13)
  - National Heart, Lung & Blood Institute: Dr. Levy
    - Correspondence. (Box 13)
    - Levy correspondence with Congressman Robert Leggett. (Box 13)
    - Presentation for NHLBI Consultation/LRI ()., March 8, 1978 (Box 13)
    - NHLBI policies attached (Robinson writings). (Box 13)
    - NHLBI policies. (Box 13)
  - NIH: Studies
    - Low-fat diet effects. (Box 13)
    - Pritikin response re LRC Study. (Box 13)
    - NIH Lipid Research Clinics Study -, 1984. (Box 13)
    - MRFIT & PEP Programs. (Box 13)
  - Federal Trade Commission; N.P. Response to FTC Charges
    - FTC (Boston), 1984. (Box 13)
    - FTC (Washington), 1983. (Box 13)
  - Senate Sub-Committee Hearings
    - Senate Committee on Labor & Human Resources, (November 1985). (Box 13)
    - Senate Sub-Committee Hearing:, February 20, 1980. (Box 13)
    - Select Senate Sub-Committee Hearing on Nutrition & Human Needs, (February 1977). (Box 13)
  - Government Agencies - Miscellaneous
    - James Iacono, Department of Agriculture. (Box 13)
    - Early grant applications investigations. (Box 13)
    - NIH, Behavioral Medical Branch. (Box 13)
    - National Institute on Aging. (Box 13)
    - Department of HEW. (Box 13)
    - U.S. Government contacts: Miscellaneous. (Box 13)
    - Carson Conrad, President's Council on Physical Fitness. (Box 13)
    - Food and Drug Administration. (Box 13)
    - Federal Judicial Center. (Box 13)
- Speaking Engagements
  - 1974
    - International Academy of Metabology, March 21-24, 1974. (Box 14)
    - American Academy of Medical Preventics, September 28, 1974. (Box 14)
    - Westside Senior Center. Santa Barbara, December 4, 1974. (Box 14)
  - 1975
    - International College of Applied Nutrition, April 18, 1975. (Box 14)
    - International Academy of Preventive Medicine, April 20, 1975. (Box 14)
    - Eastside Senior Center. Santa Barbara, June 10, 1975. (Box 14)
    - Los Angeles Atherosclerosis Group, November 6, 1975. (Box 14)
    - American Congress of Rehabilitative Medicine, November 19, 1975. (Box 14)
      (See also: Box no.5 Long Beach Study Results: Published Papers)
    - Tri-Counties Podiatric Society, December 9, 1975. (Box 14)
  - 1976
    - American Association of University Women. Ventura, January 10, 1976. (Box 14)
    - International Association of Cancer Victims and Friends, March 10, 1976. (Box 14)
    - Cosmopolitan Club, May 6, 1976. (Box 14)
    - American Nutrition Society. Pasadena, May 26, 1976. (Box 14)
    - Science and Engineering Council. Santa Barbara, June 2, 1976. (Box 14)
    - YMCA, Santa Barbara, July 30, 1976. (Box 14)
    - Santa Barbara Community Group, September 12, 1976. (Box 14)
    - International Academy of Metabology, October 2, 1976. (Box 14)
    - State University of New York, Buffalo: Dental Alumni Association, October 15, 1976. (Box 14)
    - California Association of Nurse Anasthetists, November 21, 1976. (Box 14)
    - Kiwanis Club. Santa Barbara, November 24, 1976. (Box 14)
    - Santa Barbara City College, Continuing Education, November 30, 1976. (Box 14)
    - Montecito Rotary Club, November 30, 1976. (Box 14)
    - Santa Monica: Organic Garden and Nutrition Club, December 1, 1976. (Box 14)
  - 1977
    - National Health Federation, January 30, 1977. (Box 14)
    - Hunt-Wesson Foods, February 11, 1977. (Box 14)
    - Loma Linda University: School of Health Alumni Association, March 8, 1977. (Box 14)
    - Radio Interview - NBC, March 12, 1977. (Box 14)
    - Today Show, March 16, 1977. (Box 14)
    - California Department of Health, March 18, 1977. (Box 14)
    - Torrance Memorial Hospital, March 26, 1977. (Box 14)
    - Cedars-Sinai Medical Center, April 5, 1977. (Box 14)
    - CBS-TV Filming, May 1, 1977. (Box 14)
    - Guardians of the Jewish Home for the Aged, May 3, 1977. (Box 14)
    - Helping Hand of Los Angeles, September 30, 1977. (Box 14)
    - Southern California Academy of Nutrition Research, October 1, 1977. (Box 14)
    - Energy Works, November 14, 1977. (Box 14)
    - SCIFTS - Hunt-Wesson Foods, November 16, 1977. (Box 14)
    - City of Hope, November 20, 1977. (Box 14)
    - National Running Week, December 30-31, 1977. (Box 14)
    - : Invitations to Speak (Possible Acceptance)., 1977 (Box 14)
  - 1978
    - B'nai Brith, January 10, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Vista del Mar, January 11, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Sherman Oaks Community Hospital, January 24, 1978. (Box 14)
    - San Diego State University, March 3, 1978. (Box 14)
    - American College of Cardiologists, March 6, 1978. (Box 14)
    - "AM Chicago" - TV, March 20, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Hinman Dental Meeting. Atlanta, March 22, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Nutrition Symposium. Ruth Weg, April 11, 1978. (Box 14)
    - USC, Kazarian, April 22, 1978. (Box 14)
    - American Heart Association. Greater Los Angeles, April 26, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Hofstra University. New York, May 3, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Danbury Hospital. Connecticut, May 4, 1978. (Box 14)
    - California Dental Association, May 6, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Texas Bankers Convention, May 8, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Schools Food Services. Southern California, May 12, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Southern California Permanente Medical Group, May 23, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Insurance Rehabilitative Study Group. San Diego, May 24, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Consortium of Community Colleges: TV, May 26, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Michael Jackson Talk Show, June 1, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Roberts Nutrition Symposium, June 9, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Hughes Aircraft Company, June 20, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Harold Keene Talk Show, July 30, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Salk Institute, August 1, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Rotary Club. San Diego, August 3, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Sharp Hospital. San Diego, August 4, 1978. (Box 14)
    - American Medical Writers, September 6, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Hollywood Rotary Club, September 12, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Hollywood Rotary Club, September 12, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Orthomolecular Medical Society. San Diego, September 16, 1978. (Box 14)
    - David Susskind Show. New York, October 6-7, 1978. (Box 14)
    - American Nutrition Society. Pasadena, October 25, 1978. (Box 14)
    - School of Dental Medicine. University of Pennsylvania, November 1, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Deborah Heart & Lung Center. Philadelphia, November 2, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Juvenile Diabetes Foundation. Michigan, November 3, 1978. (Box 14)
    - Leisure World. Laguna Hills, November 15, 1978. (Box 14)
  - Schedules, 1979
    - Santa Monica Track Club, January 26, 1979. (Box 14)
    - St. Joseph Medical Center, January 26, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Metropolitan Denver Dental Society, January 17, 1979. (Box 14)
    - International Conference on Gastroenterology, Family Practice Conference, February 2, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Santa Monica Hospital Medical Center, February 17, 1979. (Box 14)
    - UCLA Medicine & Society Forum, February 22, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Malibu Rotary Club, February 22, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Hunt-Wesson Foods, February 27, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Phoenix Gazette: Off & Running Seminar, March 17, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Leisure World, March 20/28, 1979. (Box 14)
    - American Geriatric Society & Dental Hospital, March 24-25, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Grosset & Dunlap Book Tour, March 30-May 10, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Southern California Permanente Medical Group. San Diego, April 5, 1979. (Box 14)
    - UC Santa Barbara, Extension, April 7, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Western Michigan University, April 20, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Ann Borgess Hospital, Cardiac Rehabilitation Symposium (Kalamazoo), April 20, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Cancer Victims Symposium (Minneapolis), April 21, 1979. (Box 14)
    - California Health Maintenance, April 26, 1979. (Box 14)
    - College of the Redwoods, May 5, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Walden School. New York, May 12, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Castle Memorial Hospital. Hawaii, May 21, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Alpha Omega Dental Fraternity. North Hollywood, May 22, 1979. (Box 14)
    - California Laundry Convention. Monterey, May 24, 1979. (Box 14)
    - University of Pennsylvania Dental Group, June 3, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Pomona Valley Community Hospital, June 5, 1979. (Box 14)
    - College of Dental Surgeons. Vancouver, B.C., June 7, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Northridge Hospital, June 19, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Daniel Freeman Memorial Hospital, June 25, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Mike Douglas Show, July 3, 1979. (Box 14)
    - St. Joseph Hospital, July 20, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Sunburst Farms. Ventura, July 30, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Southern California Permanente Medical Group. Harbor City, August 22, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Los Angeles Jr. Chamber of Commerce, September 19, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Grosset & Dunlap Book Tour, September 20-November 6, 1979. (Box 14)
    - National Institutes of Health, September 27, 1979. (Box 14)
    - University of California. Irvine. Tennessee, October 4, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Western Dental Society. Los Angeles, October 9, 1979. (Box 14)
    - American Heart Association. San Francisco, October 11, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Physicians' Post-Graduate Cardiovascular Symposium. San Francisco[?], October 12, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Orthomolecular Medical Society: Pritikin-Atkins Debate, October 14, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Cal State Fullerton, October 16, 1979. (Box 14)
    - University of California. San Diego, October 18, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Fargo (North Dakota) Clinic - Cardiovascular Symposium, October 20, 1979. (Box 14)
    - California Route Operators, October 19, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Orangewood Academy. Garden Grove, October 28, 1979. (Box 14)
    - University Connecticut School Dental Medicine/So. New England Acad. Prct. Med.[?], October 31, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Deborah Heart & Lung Center. Philadelphia, November 1, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Professional Educators Seminar. Toronto, November 2, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Dental Education, University of Pennsylvania, November 4, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Westmoreland Community College. Pennsylvania, November 7, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Swedish Covenant Hospital. Chicago, November 9, 1979. (Box 14)
    - American Heart Association. Anaheim, November 12-15, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Harbor Dental Society, November 13, 1979. (Box 14)
    - College of Osteopathic Surgeons, November 16, 1979. (Box 14)
    - National Society for Cardiovascular Technology. Maryland, November 29, 1979. (Box 14)
    - David Susskind Show, December 1, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Ambassador College. Pasadena, December 11-12, 1979. (Box 14)
    - WGST Radio Interview. Atlanta, Georgia, December 15, 1979. (Box 14)
    - Los Robles Hospital. Thousand Oaks, December 21, 1979. (Box 14)
  - Speaking Engagements:, 1976-1985
    - 1. Cancelled, refused or withdrawn. (Box 14)
    - 2. Staff invitations to speak. (Box 14)
    - 1976-1979. (Box 14)
    - 1980-1985. (Box 14)
- Speaking Engagements
  - Schedules, 1980
    - Sun Coast Heart Association. Florida, January 12, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Georgetown University Dental Society, January 18-19, 1980. (Box 15)
    - University of Iowa Cardiac Rehabilitation Program, January 22-23, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Dallas Midwinter Dental Clinic, January 27, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Phil Donahue Show, January 31, 1980. (Box 15)
    - South Bay Hospital Nutrition Symposium, February 1, 1980. (Box 15)
    - CBS News Taping, February 6, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Palm Springs Academy of Medicine, February 7-8, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Eisenhower Medical Center Post-Graduate Seminar. Palm Springs, February 7, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Round Table West, February 21, 1980. (Box 15)
    - ABC - Channel 7, March 3, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Center for Integral Medicine Conference, March 1-2, 1980. (Box 15)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Schools of Dental Medicine, March 5, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Allentown Hospital. Pennsylvania, March 5, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Jersey Shore Medical Center. New Jersey, March 6, 1980. (Box 15)
    - International Congress on Colonoscopy. Florida, March 7, 1980. (Box 15)
    - New York University Dental Education Program, March 9, 1980. (Box 15)
    - KTAR Radio (Arizona) - Interview, March 14, 1980. (Box 15)
    - PRF Fund-raising Dinner. Arizona, March 16, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Palm Beach Round Table, March 20, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Australian Book Tour (Grosset & Dunlap), March 21-April 2, 1980. (Box 15)
    - American Association of Endodontists. Los Angeles, April 19, 1980. (Box 15)
    - 4th Annual Conference, Pritikin Research Foundation, April 19-20, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Northridge Hospital Foundation Medical Center, April 22, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Boeing Management Association. Seattle, April 28, 1980. (Box 15)
    - King County Health Planning Council. Seattle, April 28, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Wisconsin Dental Association, May 4, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Northern Virginia Dental Society, May 7, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Halifax Hospital Medical Center. Florida, May 9, 1980. (Box 15)
    - St. Claire's Hospital. New Jersey, May 13, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Bergen Community College. New Jersey, May 14, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Main Line Dental Society, Lankenau Hospital. Pennsylvania, May 15, 1980. (Box 15)
    - National Management Association, Rockwell. Sherman Oaks, May 20, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Pasadena Rotary Club, May 21, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Portland Dietetic Association, May 22, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Caribbean Cruise, May 24, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Technion. Philadelphia, May 31, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Phone Interviews from Center (nation-wide radio), June 1980. (Box 15)
    - Anchorage Community College, June 6-7, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Mt. Sinai Medical Center. Milwaukee, June 12, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Swedish Covenant Hospital. Chicago, June 12, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Bantam Books: Toronto, June 13, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Professional Education Seminars. Toronto, June 14, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Florida Academy of Family Physicians, June 15, 1980. (Box 15)
    - American Heart Association. Bakersfield, June 20, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Teleconference: University of Nebraska. Lincoln, June 24, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Beverly Hills Progressive Savings & Loan, June 24, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Southern California Academy of General Dentistry, June 28, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Academy of General Dentistry. San Diego, July 2, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Leisure Village, July 25, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Taping - TV, August 7, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Media Appearances - Bantam Books. Sacramento, September 9, 1980. (Box 15)
    - New York: PR Appearances, September 21-24, 1980. (Box 15)
    - UCLA: Department of Medicine, Family Practise, October 10, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Clinical Assembly of Osteopathic Specialists. Florida, October 14, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Gottlieb Memorial Hospital. Chicago, October 15, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Alumni Meeting. Chicago, October 16, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Media Appearances - Bantam Books - Chicago, etc., October 16-31, 1980. (Box 15)
    - St. Barnabas Medical Center. New York, October 23, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Medical Joggers Association Annual Meeting, October 24-25, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Health and Fitness Fair. Ottawa, Canada, October 26, 1980. (Box 15)
    - North Mississippi Medical Center. Tupelo, November 11-12, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Santa Barbara - Ventura County Dental Association, November 20, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Annual Caduceus Conference, Kaiser Northwest, November 23, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Christmas Festival, Natchitoches. Los Angeles, December 6,1980. (Box 15)
    - TV Show "Speaking Out" - Toronto, December 11, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Mt. Sinai Hospital/American Friends of Hebrew University. New York, December 12, 1980. (Box 15)
    - American College of Cardiology. New York, December 13, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Alumni Party - Philadelphia, December 14, 1980. (Box 15)
    - TV Show - "AM-PM" - Philadelphia, December 15, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Centinela Hospital Medical Center, December 18, 1980. (Box 15)
    - Calendar: (Master Calendar/Itinerary)., 1981 (Box 16)
    - : Schedules., 1982-1984 (Box 16)
    - : Physician Audiences., 1978-1985 (Box 16)
    - : Speakers' Bureau., 1981 (Box 16)
    - Recurrent Coronary Prevention Project. San Francisco, January 16, 1981. (Box 16)
    - California Conference of Health Educators. Asilomar, February 4, 1981. (Box 16)
    - Monterey Eskaton Hospital, February 4, 1981. (Box 16)
    - Chicago Dental Society, February 14, 1981. (Box 16)
    - Bauer Hospital-St. Mary Medical Center. Long Beach, February 21, 1981. (Box 16)
    - Kaiser Permanente Medical Center, March 5, 1981. (Box 16)
    - WXYZ Radio Interview, March 30, 1981. (Box 16)
    - Broadway Department Store - Autograph PR, March 31, 1981. (Box 16)
    - Grosset & Dunlap Book Tour, April 27, 1981. (Box 16)
    - Channel 2 - "Interface,", May 7, 1981. (Box 16)
    - California Heart Association. Monterey, May 14, 1981. (Box 16)
    - St. Francis Hospital. New York, May 29, 1981. (Box 16)
    - Dialogue - "Good Food of the 80's" - New York, June 23, 1981. (Box 16)
    - San Diego Heart Institute, July 10-12, 1981. (Box 16)
    - UCLA Graduate School of Management Seminar. Ojai, July 14, 1981. (Box 16)
    - UC Irvine Health Services, July 22, 1981. (Box 16)
    - P.R. Schedules - Grosset & Dunlap Book Tour, August 30-September 4, 1981. (Box 16)
    - Bullock's Del Amo. Torrance, September 10, 1981. (Box 16)
    - TV: Taped Interviews, Cable, September 10, 1981. (Box 16)
    - California Dental Association. San Francisco, September 10, 1981. (Box 16)
    - American Medical Writers Association. New York, September 14, 1981. (Box 16)
    - American Heart Association. Reading, Pennsylvania, September 16, 1981. (Box 16)
    - Hadassah. Hartford, Connecticut, September 17, 1981. (Box 16)
    - Academy of General Dentistry. Hartford, September 17, 1981. (Box 16)